

MAKE SIMPLE BUT MORE.

SUMMARY

HELLO,

My name is CJ. I am a web engineer and software developer with three years' experience in B2B software and P.O.S application. Specializes in front end development with react/redux, angularJS and hybrid mobile application.

Loves to write code in high-paced and challenging environment to deliver high-quality and maintainable product. Working fast and considerate in the agile way.

I am also the co-organizer of F2E&RGBA monthly meetup. Enjoys learning new technologies and sharing experiences, new findings with friends and colleagues.

CONTACT

NAME: EMAIL:

XI JIE TAN 陳熙杰 cijies@gmail.com

NATIONALITY: WEBSITE: Malaysian www.cjies.com

DATE OF BIRTH:29 September 1991

SOCIAL LINKS:

www.github.com/cjies

www.linkedin.com/cjies

PHONE: www.speakerdeck.com/cjies
+886 978 109 929

TECHNICAL SKILLS / LANGUAGES

WEB DEVELOPMENT

React / Redux

Sass

2013 - present

Jest / enzyme - testing

Django - python

lonic - angularJS

Codelgniter - php

2015 - present

2016 - present

2016 - present

2014 - 2016

2013 - 2014

LANGUAGES

Mandarin Native
English Fluent
Cantonese Fluent
Japanese Advanced
Malay Intermediate

CJIES TAN
Front End Engineer

EDUCATION / DEGREES

2010 - 2014 BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING

National Cheng Kung University, Tainan

2004 - 2009 SCIENCE CLASS, HIGH SCHOOL

Pay Fong High School, Melaka Malaysia

EXPERIENCES

iCHEF CO. LTD.

Mar 2016 - Present

Front End Developer

- Developed a web CMS application for restaurant POS.
- Designed and coded a large in-house component library with react.
- Created a cross-platform deploy tool to deliver products easier and faster.
- Participated in community-organized meetups to sharing experiences.

Tech skills: React / Redux, AngularJS, Django, Sass, Electron, etc.

Joined Projects: iCHEF components library, Restaurant printer settings,

TW e-invoice management and etc.

GALAXY SOFTWARE SERVICES

Sep 2014 - Feb 2016

Front End Engineer

- Positioned as main front-end engineer in design team.
- Architectured a common build scripts for web development.
- Developed Taipei 1999 mobile application for iOS and Android.
- Worked with software developers from different departments to building a large software applications.

Tech skills: AngularJS, Ionic, Cordova, Kendo, .net MVC

Joined Projects: Payroll system, Document System, Government projects

ART SERVICES @ ART CENTER, NCKU Web Developer & Designer (Part-time) Jun 2014 - July 2014

- Created a website to show the arts information.
- Developed backend database, API services and front end pages.
- Designed the website UI.

Tech skills: Codelgniter, JQuery, MySQL

CJIES TAN 0978 109 929
Front End Engineer cijies@gmail.com

JOINED PROJECTS

iCHEF Components Library

Apr 2016 - Present

Front End Developer @ iCHEF Co. Ltd

iC-framework is an in-house web components library built with react. We tried to build a sharable and extendable library that can be easily applied in any iCHEF web applications and delivering our products faster.

- Played as the core contributor.
- Architectured the library base and build scripts.
- Collaborated with UI / UX designer to complete the design patterns.
- Interacted with Jenkins CI, deploy the library automatically.

Tech skills: React, Sass, Webpack, Jest, Enzyme, etc.

Restaurant Printer Settings

Mar 2016 - Sep 2016

Front End Developer @ iCHEF Co. Ltd

Restaurant printer settings is a core feature in iCHEF web CMS application. My primary job is trying to refactor the out-fashioned and AngularJS based application into React / Redux base. This is also the first project that implemented with our iCHEF components library.

- Developed the web UI and layouts.
- Managed and the UI actions with saga pattern.
- Worked with backend engineer to concatenate the API services.
- Fixed localization problem with i18next and Lokalise.

Tech skills: React, Redux, Webpack, Django, i18next, etc.

Taipei 1999 Mobile App

Sep 2015 - Jan 2016

Lead Front End Engineer @ GSS

Taipei 1999 (also named 台北市單一陳情系統) is a hybrid mobile application which built with Ionic framework and AngularJS. Leading two front-end developers to develop high-quality software and deliver faster with Agile methodology.

- Played as the lead front end engineer.
- Designed the architecture for whole project.
- Created and customized Angular modules and plugins.
- Implemented the API and Angular application, with optimizations for primarily targeting mobile platforms.

Tech skills: Ionic, AngularJS, Cordova, Sass, Gulp, etc.

CJIES TAN
Front End Engineer

0978 109 929

JOINED PROJECTS

TW E-invoice Management System Front End Developer @ iCHEF Co. Ltd

Oct 2016 - Jan 2017

TW e-invoice management system is a system to let users upload and manage their invoice data in our web CMS. We also launched a dashboard to recognize data missing issues, reduced errors from 20% to less than 1%.

- Refactored out-fashioned system into React / Redux base.
- Handled complex form validation and UI flows.
- Worked with backend engineer to concatenate the API services.
- Created in-house dashboard to monitor invoice issues.

Tech skills: React, Redux Form, Django, etc.

Vital Payroll System

Oct 2014 - Jun 2015

Front End Designer / Engineer @ GSS

Vital payroll system is a cloud based software designed to organize all the task of employee payment and the filing of employee taxes. This is also a cross BU team project, played as a designer and front end engineer to solve the UI designs and front end development issues.

- Designed software UI.
- Customized Kendo components and plugins.
- $\mbox{\sc Prototyped}$ a mobile application with ionic framework.
- Collaborated with different B.U. teams.

Tech skills: AngularJS, Ionic, Sass, Kendo, .net MVC, etc.

CJIES TAN
Front End Engineer